[
  {
    "front": null,
    "back": "Official Website"
  },
  {
    "front": null,
    "back": "JavaScript Cheat Sheet [.pdf]"
  },
  {
    "front": null,
    "back": "JavaScript Quick Reference Card [.pdf]"
  },
  {
    "front": null,
    "back": "JavaScript and Browser Objects Quick Reference [.pdf]"
  },
  {
    "front": null,
    "back": "JavaScript in one page"
  },
  {
    "front": "AJAX Cheat Sheet",
    "back": "AJAX"
  },
  {
    "front": "CSS Cheat Sheet",
    "back": "CSS"
  },
  {
    "front": "HTML DOM Cheat Sheet",
    "back": "HTML DOM"
  },
  {
    "front": "GWT Cheat Sheet",
    "back": "GWT"
  },
  {
    "front": "HTML Cheat Sheet",
    "back": "HTML"
  },
  {
    "front": "jQuery Cheat Sheet",
    "back": "jQuery"
  },
  {
    "front": "MooTools Cheat Sheet",
    "back": "MooTools"
  },
  {
    "front": "Node.js Cheat Sheet",
    "back": "Node.js"
  },
  {
    "front": "Prototype Cheat Sheet",
    "back": "Prototype"
  },
  {
    "front": "XHTML Cheat Sheet",
    "back": "XHTML"
  }
]
